Register of the Romanov family papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Princess Tat'iana Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) papers from red trunk no. 6, 1847-1991
  - Correspondence, 1911-1945
    - Nef, Ol'ga, 1924-1940 (Reel 31)
      Box/Folder 24: 3
    - Nesterovskaia, Antonina Rafailovna, 1922-1927
      Box/Folder 24: 4
    - Nikolai Nikolaevich, Grand Duke of Russia, 1924
      Box/Folder 24: 5
    - Nikolaieva, Evgeniia, 1942
      Box/Folder 24: 6
    - Nina Bagration-Mukhranskaia, Princess, 1911-1913
      Box/Folder 24: 7
    - Ol'ga Aleksandrovna, Grand Duchess of Russia, 1922
      Box/Folder 24: 8
    - Ol'ga, Princess of Greece and Denmark, 1940 (Reel 32)
      Box/Folder 24: 9
    - Olsuf'ev (Olsoufieff), Mikhail, 1940
      Box/Folder 24: 10
    - Olsuf'eva, Tat'iana, 1922-1942
      Box/Folder 24: 11
    - Orlova, E., 1942
      Box/Folder 24: 12
    - Orlova, Mariia, circa 1925
      Box/Folder 24: 13
    - Pepanow, T., 1937-1939
      Box/Folder 24: 14
    - Poznanskaia, Natal'ia, 1924-1940
      Box/Folder 24: 15
    - Prosch, Georg, 1942
      Box/Folder 24: 16
    - Putiatin, Sofia, circa 1925
      Box/Folder 24: 17
    - Reibold de la Tour, Ellen, 1942
      Box/Folder 24: 18
    - Rostkov, G., 1940
      Box/Folder 24: 19
    - Rostov, Dmitrii, 1924
      Box/Folder 24: 20
    - Saksonskii, Mark (Marc), 1940-1942
      Box/Folder 24: 21
    - Schleiffer, C., 1942
      Box/Folder 24: 22
    - Schulenburg, M. and V., 1922
      Box/Folder 24: 23
    - Shakhovskoi, Vladimir Aleksandrovich, 1922
      Box/Folder 24: 24
    - Sheremetev, Sergei, 1924-1943
      Box/Folder 24: 25
    - Sheremeteva-Fabergé, Tatiana, 1942
      Box/Folder 24: 26
    - Shkuro, Andrei, 1931
      Box/Folder 24: 27
    - Smirnov (Smirnoff), Sergei (Serge), 1940-1941
      Box/Folder 24: 28
    - Souller, G., 1922
      Box/Folder 24: 29
    - Suillerat, Cecile, 1940-1943
      Box/Folder 24: 30
    - Sviatopolk-Mirskaia, Sofiia, 1940
      Box/Folder 24: 31
    - Tasso, Nicolas
      Box/Folder 24: 32
    - Tecol, M., 1938
      Box/Folder 24: 33
    - Teimuraz (Teymuraz) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich) Bagration-Mukhranskii, Prince, 1927-1941 (Reels 32-33)
      Box/Folder 24: 34-42 (Folders 34-38 on Reel 32, Folders 39-42 on Reel 33)
    - Teimurazi (Racic), Katarina, 1942 (Reel 33)
      Box/Folder 25: 1
    - Tumanova, Nina, 1940
      Box/Folder 25: 2
    - Union de Banques Suisses, 1924
      Box/Folder 25: 3
    - Vertranensstelle, Rubische, 1937
      Box/Folder 25: 4
    - Voiekov, N., 1940
      Box/Folder 25: 5
    - Willis, Helen, circa 1930
      Box/Folder 25: 6
    - Witteveen, Maria, 1940
      Box/Folder 25: 7
    - Calling and business cards with written notes, 1922-1942
      Box/Folder 25: 8
    - Draft letters, 1940-1942
      Box/Folder 25: 9
    - Unidentified, 1922-1945
      Box/Folder 25: 10-16
  - Subject file, 1887-1969
    - Princess Tat'iana Konstantinovna's (Constantinovna) leisure activities file, 1929-1942
      Box/Folder 25: 17-18
      Includes boat boarding pass, notes, sketches, programs, and clippings.
    - Grand Duke Konstantin (Constantin) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich) file, 1887-1969
      - Letters to his wife Elisabeth, 1887
        Box/Folder 25: 19
      - Copy of documents proving that Prince Konstantin (Constantin) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich) along with his brothers Prince Ioann Konstantinovich (Constantinovich) and Prince Igor Konstantinovich (Constantinovich) were buried in the Russian Orthodox Church cemetery in Beijing, 1919-1920
        Box/Folder 25: 20
      - "Grand Duke's Last Great Confession," recollection by priest Leonid Kolchev, 1924 (Reel 34)
        Box/Folder 25: 21
      - Vstrecha s velikim kniazem Konstantinom Konstantinovichem, eyewitness account of Grand Duke and his family crossing Eastern Front lines on their return to Russia from Germany in 1914, by P. Isheev, 1969
        Box/Folder 25: 22
    - Russian Orthodox Church outside Russia file, 1923-1938
      - Princess Tat'iana Konstantinovna (Constantinovna), notes on religion, 1923-1926
        Box/Folder 25: 23
      - Blessing of Russian Orthodox Cathedral in Berlin, 1938
        Box/Folder 25: 24
        Includes a text on German governmental document recognizing Berlin Russian Orthodox Church as the "first" Orthodox church in a non-Orthodox country.
  - Financial documents, 1932-1942
    Box/Folder 25: 25-28
  - Photographs and photo postcards, 1847-1991
    Photographs arranged alphabetically by name.
    - General, 1902-1925
      Box/Folder 26: 1-3
      Includes postcards depicting members of royal families
    - Aleksandr II of Russia, circa 1870
      Box/Folder 26: 4
    - Aleksandr III of Russia, circa 1880
      Box/Folder 26: 5
    - Aleksandra Iosifovna, Grand Duchess of Russia, 1879-1911 (Reel 35)
      Box/Folder 26: 6
    - Andrei Vladimirovich, Grand Duke of Russia, circa 1920
      Box/Folder 26: 7
    - Andrew, Prince of Greece and Denmark and Princess Alice of Battenberg's silver wedding anniversary, 1928
      Box/Folder 26: 8
    - Anna Feodorovna, Grand Duchess of Russia, circa 1880
      Box/Folder 26: 9
    - Blausevich, O., circa 1910
      Box/Folder 26: 10
    - Boris Vladimirovich, Grand Duke of Russia, 1880-1911
      Box/Folder 26: 11
    - Dmitrii Konstantinovich (Constantinovich), Grand Duke of Russia, 1867-1913
      Box/Folder 26: 12
    - Dmitrii Pavlovich, Grand Duke of Russia, circa 1910
      Box/Folder 26: 13
    - Elena Pavlovna, Grand Duchess of Russia (Princess Charlotte of Württemberg), circa 1870
      Box/Folder 26: 14
    - Elizaveta Feodorovna, Grand Duchess of Russia, circa 1910
      Box/Folder 26: 15
    - Elizaveta Mavrikievna, Grand Duchess of Russia, 1884-1921
      Box/Folder 26: 16
    - Gavriil (Gabriel) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich), Prince of Russia, 1907-1938
      Box/Folder 26: 17
      Includes family photos.
    - Georgii (Georgy) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich), Prince of Russia, 1920
      Box/Folder 26: 18
    - Georgii Mikhailovich, Grand Duke of Russia, circa 1900
      Box/Folder 26: 19
    - Igor Konstantinovich (Constantinovich), Prince of Russia, circa 1910
      Box/Folder 26: 20
    - Kirill (Cyril) Vladimirovich, Grand Duke of Russia, circa 1920
      Box/Folder 26: 21
    - Konstantin (Constantin) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich) Grand Duke and Grand Duchess Elizaveta Mavrikievna, 1880-1906
      Box/Folder 26: 22-23, 27: 1-2
    - Konstantin (Constantin) Nikolaevich, Grand Duke and his eldest son Grand Duke Nikolai Konstantinovich (Constantinovich), circa 1860
      Box/Folder 27: 3
    - Ksenia (Xenia) Aleksandrovna, Grand Duchess of Russia, 1914
      Box/Folder 27: 4
    - Marie, Princess of Edinburgh (Marie of Romania), 1919-1934
      Box/Folder 27: 5
    - Maria Feodorovna, Dowager Empress of Russia, 1847-1866
      Box/Folder 27: 6
    - Mikhail Aleksandrovich, Grand Duke of Russia, 1914
      Box/Folder 27: 7
    - Mikhail Mikhailovich, Grand Duke of Russia, 1884
      Box/Folder 27: 8
    - Mikhail Nikolaevich, Grand Duke of Russia, circa 1900
      Box/Folder 27: 9
    - Natal'ia Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) Bagration-Mukhranskaia-Johnston, Princess, circa 1950
      Box/Folder 27: 10
    - Nicholas II of Russia, 1889-1918
      - General, 1891-1918
        Arranged chronologically.
        - Portraits, 1891-1918
          Box/Folder 27: 11-12
        - Participating in military parades and public celebrations, 1897-1914 (Reels 35-36)
          Box/Folder 27: 13-14 (Folder 13 on Reel 35, Folder 14 on Reel 36)
        - Leib-Gvardii Gusarskii Ego Velichestva Polk, 1912 (Reel 36)
          Box/Folder 27: 15
      - Romanov Royal Family, 1889-1918
        Arranged alphabetically by name.
        - Aleksandra Feodorovna, Empress Consort of all Russia, 1889-1918
          Box/Folder 27: 16-17
        - Aleksei Nikolaevich, Tsarevich of Russia, circa 1910
          27: 18, 28: 1-2
        - Anastasiia Nikolaevna and Mariia Nikolaevna, Grand Duchesses of Russia, 1903-1918
          Box/Folder 28: 3
        - O'lga Nikolaevna and Tat'iana Nikolaevna, Grand Duchesses of Russia, 1895-1918
          Box/Folder 28: 4-5
    - Nicholas, Prince of Greece and Denmark, circa 1900
      Box/Folder 28: 6
    - Nicholas Konstantinovich (Constantinovich), Grand Duke of Russia, circa 1870
      Box/Folder 28: 7
    - Nicholas Nikolaevich, Grand Duke of Russia, 1889-1924
      Box/Folder 28: 8
    - Oleg Konstantinovich (Constantinovich), Prince of Russia, 1903-1914
      Box/Folder 28: 9
    - Ol'ga Aleksandrovna, Grand Duchess of Russia, 1914-1916
      Box/Folder 28: 10
    - Ol'ga Konstantinovna (Constantinovna), Grand Duchess of Russia, circa 1910
      Box/Folder 28: 11
    - Roman Petrovich, Prince of Russia, and Princess Praskovia Dmitrievna, circa 1925
      Box/Folder 28: 12
    - "Rossiiskoe Imperatorskoe Diplomaticheskoe Agentstvo v Kaire,", 1913 December 6-19
      Box/Folder 28: 13
    - Sergei Aleksandrovich, Grand Duke of Russia, 1901
      Box/Folder 28: 14
    - Tat'iana Konstantinovna (Constantinovna), Princess of Russia, 1891-1920 (Reels 36-37)
      Box/Folder 28: 15-16 (Folder 15 on Reel 36, Folder 16 on Reel 37)
    - Teimuraz (Teymuraz) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich) Bagration-Mukhranskii, Prince, 1913-1916 (Reel 37)
      Box/Folder 28: 17
    - Vera Konstantinovna (Constantinovna), Princess of Russia, 1907-1991
      Box/Folder 28: 18-20
    - Viktoria Feodorovna, Grand Duchess of Russia, 1913-1917
      Box/Folder 28: 21
    - Unidentified, circa 1900
      Box/Folder 28: 22
    - Photocopies of photographs, 1894-1919
      Box/Folder 28: 23
- Princess Tat'iana Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) papers from the dark fabric bag, 1919-1992
  - Personal file, 1919-1992
    - Passport issued by the Georgian Embassy in Kiev, Ukraine, 1919
      Box/Folder 29: 1
    - Biographical data, 1992
      Box/Folder 29: 2
  - Correspondence, 1920-1985
    - General, 1921-1936
      Box/Folder 29: 3-5
    - Invitations, 1936
      Box/Folder 29: 6
    - ABC Magazine, 1936
      Box/Folder 29: 7
    - Adamovich, Boris, 1929
      Box/Folder 29: 8
    - Alexander I, King of Yugoslavia, 1933
      Box/Folder 29: 9
    - Aleksei (Alexis) Bagration, Prince, 1934-1936
      Box/Folder 29: 10
    - "Ata" (Emma Karlovna Shadovets), nanny, 1935
      Box/Folder 29: 11
    - Bagration-Mukhranskaia, Mariia, 1936
      Box/Folder 29: 12
    - Bossar, Eugenia, 1935-1936
      Box/Folder 29: 13
    - Chetwynd, Augusta, 1936
      Box/Folder 29: 14
    - Depreiss, Irina, 1935
      Box/Folder 29: 15
    - Elizaveta Mavrikievna, Grand Duchess of Russia, 1920-1926 (Reels 37-38)
      Box/Folder 29: 16-21 (Folders 16-20 on Reel 37, Folder 21 on Reel 38)
    - Gavriil (Gabriel) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich), Prince of Russia, 1936 (Reel 38)
      Box/Folder 29: 22
    - Guillerat, Cecile, 1936
      Box/Folder 29: 23
    - Hoffmann-Sokolovskaia, Elena, circa 1936
      Box/Folder 29: 24
    - Horneffer, S. Ch., circa 1936
      Box/Folder 29: 25
    - Ivanov, G., circa 1970
      Box/Folder 29: 26
    - Kantakuzin, Konstantin and Ekaterina (Katia), 1935-1936
      Box/Folder 29: 27
    - Kepping, Boris Mikhailovich Von, 1938
      Box/Folder 29: 28
    - Korochentsoff, Aleksei and Lilly, 1936
      Box/Folder 29: 29
    - Ksenia (Xenia) Aleksandrovna, Grand Duchess of Russia, circa 1936
      Box/Folder 29: 30
    - Kullmann (Kul'man), Mariia Mikhailovna, 1926-1936
      Box/Folder 29: 31
    - Kutaisova, M., circa 1936
      Box/Folder 29: 32
    - Leikhtenbergskaia, Mariia, 1936
      Box/Folder 29: 33
    - Mitchell (Edgley), Maria M., 1936
      Box/Folder 29: 34
    - Murav'eva-Apostol, N., 1933-1936
      Box/Folder 29: 35
    - Natal'ia Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) Bagration-Mukhranskaia-Johnston, Princess, 1926-1971
      Box/Folder 29: 36-37
    - Nef, Ol'ga, 1936
      Box/Folder 29: 38
    - Nesterovskaia, Antonina Rafailovna, 1934-1935
      Box/Folder 29: 39
    - Orlov (Orloff), Sergei (Serge), 1935-1936
      Box/Folder 29: 40
    - Orlova, Mariia, 1936
      Box/Folder 29: 41
    - Reymond, G., 1936
      Box/Folder 30: 1
    - Roman Petrovich, Prince of Russia, 1967-1968
      Box/Folder 30: 2
    - Savchenko, Petr, 1932-1936
      Box/Folder 30: 3
    - Sheremetev, Sergei and Tatiana, 1936
      Box/Folder 30: 4
    - Smirnov (Smirnoff), Sergei (Serge), 1935-1936
      Box/Folder 30: 5
    - Sviatopolk-Mirskaia, Sofiia, 1935-1936
      Box/Folder 30: 6
    - Taylor, Janet, 1936
      Box/Folder 30: 7
    - Teimuraz (Teymuraz) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich) Bagration-Mukhranskii, Prince, 1925-1979 (Reels 38-39)
      Box/Folder 30: 8-19 (Folders 8-14 on Reel 38, Folders 15-19 on Reel 39)
    - Vera Konstantinovna (Constantinovna), Princess of Russia, 1936-1973 (Reel 39)
      Box/Folder 30: 20
    - Vil'chkovskii, Sergei, 1926
      Box/Folder 30: 21
    - Vladimir Kirillovich, Grand Duke of Russia, 1938-1985
      Box/Folder 30: 22
      Includes materials relating to the article "O chem oni mechtaiut," Pravda, December 16, 1984, as well as letters from the Union Internationale Monarchiste.
    - Tat'iana Konstantinovna's (Constantinovna), Princess of Russia, draft letters, 1935-1939
      Box/Folder 30: 23
  - Russian Orthodox Church in Paris and Geneva file, 1936-1939
    - Correspondence, 1936-1939
      Box/Folder 30: 24
    - Documents relating to the Church's activities and events, 1936
      Box/Folder 30: 25
  - Financial documents, 1935-1936
    Box/Folder 30: 26-27
  - Clippings and other printed matter, 1936
    Box/Folder 30: 28
- Prince Teimuraz (Teymuraz) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich) Bagration-Mukhranskii papers from the dark fabric bag, 1920-1980
  - Correspondence, 1920-1980
    - Antonii, Metropolitan, 1928-1930
      Box/Folder 31: 1
    - Elizaveta Mavrikievna, Grand Duchess of Russia, 1920-1926
      Box/Folder 31: 2
    - Feodosii, Hieromonk, 1929
      Box/Folder 31: 3
    - Gavriil (Gabriel) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich), Prince of Russia, 1929-1931
      Box/Folder 31: 4
    - Ksenia (Xenia) Aleksandrovna, Grand Duchess of Russia, 1957
      Box/Folder 31: 5
    - Mikhail Gagarin, Prince, circa 1960
      Box/Folder 31: 6
      Includes copy of telegram from Nicholas II to his brother Grand Duke Mikhail, after Tsar's abdication.
    - Natal'ia Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) Bagration-Mukhranskaia-Johnston, Princess, 1927-1931
      Box/Folder 31: 7
    - Nina Bagration-Mukhranskaia, Princess, circa 1925
      Box/Folder 31: 8
    - Theoktista, Mother, 1980
      Box/Folder 31: 9
    - Vera Konstantinovna (Constantinovna), Princess of Russia, 1929-1932
      Box/Folder 31: 10
  - Photographs depicting family members, 1929-1931
    Box/Folder 31: 11
- Princess Vera Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) papers from the dark fabric bag, 1927-1994
  - Personal file, 1928-1945
    - Certificate of alien registration, Germany, 1928
      Box/Folder 31: 12
    - Travel certificate issued by the Synod of Bishops of the Russian Orthodox Church Abroad, Munich, 1945
      Box/Folder 31: 13
  - Correspondence, 1936-1994
    - Chertkova, M., 1994
      Box/Folder 31: 14
    - Kepping, Boris Mikhailovich Von, 1937-1938
      Box/Folder 31: 15
      Includes Vysochaishe utverzhdennyi Tseremonial o sviatom kreshchenii Ego Vysochestva Kniazia Imperatorskoi Krovi Igoria Konstantinovicha.
    - Magerovskii, Lev, 1976
      Box/Folder 31: 16
      Includes letters regarding Prince Gabriel Konstantinovich's and Princess Vera Konstantinovna's memoirs.
    - Unidentified, 1936 (Reel 40)
      Box/Folder 31: 17
  - Writings, "Posle voiny," memoirs, 1927-1955
    Box/Folder 31: 18
- "In the Marbal Palace," by Prince Gavriil (Gabriel) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich), manuscript from the dark fabric bag, 1946 (Reels 40-42)
  31: 19-30 (Reel 40), 32: 1-15 (Folders 1-5 on Reel 40, Folders 6-15 on Reel 41), 33: 1-6 (Folders 1-3 on Reel 41, Folders 4-6 on Reel 42)
- The Russian Orthodox Church Outside of Russia vs. The Orthodox Palestine Society, the Holy Land Section from the dark fabric bag, 1990-1991 (Reel 42)
  Box/Folder 33: 7-8
- Printed matter from carton no. 1, 1954-2001
  Arranged chronologically. See also: Oversize materials.
  - "Moi vospominaniia, 1875-1946," by Prince G. N. Eristov (Eristoff), 1954
    Box/Folder 33: 9
  - Le Grand Duc Héritier de Russie Nicolas Alexandrovitch, by E. Fricero, 1958
    Box/Folder 33: 10
  - Association of Russian Imperial Naval Officers in America, Inc, Bulletin No. 9/136, 1977
    Box/Folder 33: 11
  - Imperial Russian Journal, Volume 5, No. 3, 2001
    Box/Folder 33: 12
- Carton no. 3 [See: "Dark fabric bag"]
- Carton no. 4 [See: Oversize materials]
- Printed matter from carton no. 5, 1882-1997
  - Izvlechenia iz" picem" Gosudaria Velikago Kniazia Konstantina Nikolaevicha k" Stats"-Sekretariu Golovninu, typescript, 1882
    Box/Folder 33: 13
  - Avgustieishii poet" K. R., by N. N. Sergievskii, Petrograd, 1915
    Box/Folder 33: 14
  - "Kavalergardy sredi Leib"- Erivantsev". 1915 god"," Sarajevo, Yugoslavia, 1934
    Box/Folder 33: 15
    Includes copies belonging to Aleksandr Pashkov and Sergei (Serge) Bezobrazov (Bezobrazoff), V. Shidel'skii's letter to Aleksandr Pashkov, and a list of deceased Chevaliers Gardes to be read at the church service on September 18, on the regimental fete day.
  - Koroleva Ellinov" Ol'ga Konstantinovna, by M. IU. Garshin, Praga, 1937
    Box/Folder 33: 16
  - Kavalergardy v" Velikuiu i Grazhdanskuiu voinu, 1914-1920 god", by V. N. Zvegintsov, Paris, 1938 (Reel 43)
    Box/Folder 34: 1
  - Pamiati Posliedniago Tsaria, by Kirill Zaitsev, Shanghai, 1948
    Box/Folder 34: 2
  - Pamiati Ego Imperatorskgo Vysochestva Valikago Kniazia Konstantina Konstantinovicha (K. R.), New York, 1956
    Box/Folder 34: 3
  - "Eti milye Dve bukvy ...," by N. Sergievskii, New York, 1957
    Box/Folder 34: 4
  - Koroleva Ellinov" Ol'ga Konstantinovna, by V. Poliakov and M. Garshin, 1959
    Box/Folder 34: 5
  - Leib-Erivatsy v Velikoi voine, edited by K. Popov, Paris, 1959
    Box/Folder 34: 6
  - Sbornik pamiati Velikogo Kniazia Konstantina Konstantinovicha poeta K. R., edited by A. Gering, Paris, 1962-1969
    Box/Folder 34: 7
    Includes clippings and post cards.
  - Kavalergardy dekabristy, dopolnenie k sborniku biografii kavalergardov 1801-1826, by V. N. Zviantsov, Paris, 1977
    Box/Folder 34: 8
  - Russkaia literatura, No. 2, Saint Petersburg, 1993 (Reel 44)
    Box/Folder 34: 9
  - Avgusteishii prezident, by V. S. Sobolev, Saint Petersburg, 1993
    Box/Folder 34: 10
  - Avgusteishii poet, by L. I. Kuz'mina, Saint Petersburg, 1995
    Box/Folder 35: 1
  - "Velikii kniaz'," Istoricheskii sbornik, No. 1, New York, 1996
    Box/Folder 35: 2
  - Dlia tebia, by L. S. Teplova, 1997
    Box/Folder 35: 3
- Princess Vera Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) papers from carton no. 6, 1898-1992
  - Correspondence, 1920-1950
    - General, 1929-1942
      Box/Folder 35: 4-7
    - Coutard, E. M., circa 1925
      Box/Folder 35: 8
    - Elizaveta Mavrikievna, Grand Duchess of Russia, 1925-1927
      Box/Folder 35: 9
    - Hass, Fritz, 1937
      Box/Folder 35: 10
    - Mordvinov, A., 1937
      Box/Folder 35: 11
    - Ol'ga, Princess of Greece and Denmark, 1922-1929
      Box/Folder 35: 12
    - Taube, E., circa 1925
      Box/Folder 35: 13
    - Vsevolod Ioannovich, Prince of Russia, 1920
      Box/Folder 35: 14
    - Willaredt, Marie, 1950
      Box/Folder 35: 15
  - Photographs, 1898-1992
    - General, undated
      Box/Folder 35: 16
    - M. S. Bezobrazova "Vorobushek',", undated
      Box/Folder 35: 17
    - Prince Georgii (Georgy) Konstantinovich, undated
      Box/Folder 35: 18
    - Imperatorskii Aleksandrovskii Litsei, undated
      Box/Folder 35: 19
    - Princess Kira Kirillovna and her family, undated
      Box/Folder 35: 20
    - "Strelna, Orianda, Yalta," photo album, undated
      Box/Folder 35: 21
      Contains photographs depicting Grand Duke Konstantin (Constantin) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich) and Princess Tatiana Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) with brothers, as well as palaces and landscapes.
    - "Zakrytoe zasedanie Priamurskago Velikago Sobora,", undated
      Box/Folder 35: 22
    - St. Petersburg scenes, 1898
      Box/Folder 35: 23
    - "Roman - Elsa - Nina,", 1921
      Box/Folder 35: 24
    - Don Kosaken Chor at Dresden, 1924
      Box/Folder 35: 25
    - Princess Vera Konstantinovna's (Constantinovna's) portraits, 1930-1950 (Reel 45)
      Box/Folder 35: 26
    - Prince Teimuraz (Teymuraz) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich) Bagration-Mukhranskii, 1937
      Box/Folder 35: 27
    - Princess Helene of Serbia, 1941
      Box/Folder 35: 28
    - Prince Roman Petrovich and his wife Princess Praskov'ia Dmitrievna, Alexandria, Egypt, 1952
      Box/Folder 35: 29
    - Princess Vera Konstantinovna's (Constantinovna's) portraits, 1953
      Box/Folder 35: 30
    - 30th Anniversary of the Russian Holy Fathers Church, New York, 1957
      Box/Folder 35: 31
    - Marine Ball, New York, 1957
      Box/Folder 35: 32
    - Princess Vera Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) at various events, 1958-1959
      Box/Folder 36: 1-2
    - Princess Vera Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) with Lieutenant Gladkii, 1960
      Box/Folder 36: 3
    - "Vera, Liviia, Olga,", 1964
      Box/Folder 36: 4
    - "200-letnii Iubilei Imperatorskago Vospitatel'nago Obshchestva Blagorodnykh Devits (Smol'nyi), New York,", 1964
      Box/Folder 36: 5
    - Anna Marly, 1965
      Box/Folder 36: 6
    - Princess Vera Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) at various events, 1967
      Box/Folder 36: 7
    - "Den' Russkago Rebenka,", 1967
      Box/Folder 36: 8
    - "Vecher zarubezhnykh kadet,", 1967
      Box/Folder 36: 9
    - Princess Vera Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) at church events, 1968
      Box/Folder 36: 10
    - "Detskoe obshchestvo,", 1968
      Box/Folder 36: 11
    - Georgievskii prazdnik, New York, 1968
      Box/Folder 36: 12
    - Jerusalem trip, 1968
      Box/Folder 36: 13
    - Cadet congresses, Canada, 1968-1969
      Box/Folder 36: 14
    - Greece trip, 1969
      Box/Folder 36: 15
    - "Bal Vitiazei,", 1971
      Box/Folder 36: 16
    - The Fourth Congress of the Russian Foreign Cadet Corps, San Francisco, 1974
      Box/Folder 36: 17-21
    - At the Russian Orthodox Monastery in Jordanville, New York, 1974
      Box/Folder 36: 22
    - Prince Fedor Nikitich, 1975
      Box/Folder 36: 23
    - With Russian community in Venezuela, 1975
      Box/Folder 36: 24-26
    - Ksenia Shtrandmann, 1975
      Box/Folder 36: 27
    - Princess Vera Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) at church events, 1976
      Box/Folder 36: 28
    - Princess Vera Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) at various events, 1977-1979
      Box/Folder 36: 29
    - At Sviato-Troitskii monastyr', 1977-1980
      Box/Folder 36: 30
    - With Prince Nikita, 1977-1979
      Box/Folder 36: 31
    - "Proslavlenie I. R. Bonner,", 1981
      Box/Folder 36: 32
    - Princess Vera Konstantinovna's (Constantinovna's) portraits, 1982
      Box/Folder 37: 1
    - Cadet congress, 1986-1988
      Box/Folder 37: 2
    - With Aleksei and Valentina, 1989
      Box/Folder 37: 3
    - At Tolstoi Foundation, 1992
      Box/Folder 37: 4
- Princess Tatiana Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) papers from carton no. 6, 1900-1990
  - Altenburg-Grand Duchess Elizaveta Mavrikievna's homeland, collection of printed matter, 1900-1990
    Box/Folder 37: 5-9
    Includes postcards, brochures, and city maps.
  - Romanov Royal Family tree cards, circa 1940
    Box/Folder 37: 10
  - "Torzhestvennoe sobranie pamiati E. I. V. Vel. Kn. Konstantina Konstantinovicha, 19 Oktiabria 1958. Dokladchiki: Krushinskii, Meier, Rerberg, Korius," sound recording, 1/4-inch x 7-inch sound tape reel (Reel 46)
    Box/Folder 37: 11 (only papers within folder were filmed)